# Rabeea Ali Mustafa

dob: 21 Mar 1995 address: Duhok,IQ tel: +9647508213035 email: rabieali520@gmail.com

linkedin: linkedin.com/in/rabeea-ali github: github: github.com/rabeeaAli personal: rabeea.me

## **Skills Summary**

7+ years of web application development experience and a passion for innovative technologies. I'm looking for a position where I can build great platforms for scalability on the Internet.

**Topics of interest:** Web Application Development, Real-time Apps, Chat Bots Design, Cloud Computing, System Design, Database Design and Optimization, Data Structures, and UI/UX Development.

#### **Experience**

#### **Software Developer**

**Bandtech** 

January 2021 - Present

I'm a Backend and DevOps specialist in the company, I've set up a big corporate structure in terms of server control and building the company's infrastructure and completely dependent on AWS, I've done many solutions for medical companies, including mobile apps that help companies solve big problems they faced.

#php(laravel) #vuejs #mysql #redis #ci-cd #ec2 #codepipeline #rds #docker #gihub

#### **Software Developer**

Salla

March 2020 - January 2021

I worked there as a Technical Support Developer, and it was one of the most wonderful places where I worked as a debugger for the company's code and fixed the most important problems and errors contained in the project, and also provided some solutions, and dealt with a large amount of data of products and requests.

#### Software Developer

Freelancer

March 2015 - 2020

In this fun journey I accomplished a lot of things from, I used Laravel framework for web, Tailwind CSS framework for design, then writing features and unit testing was one of my priorities, dealt with API in a professional way for backend, then plunged into the world of e-commerce, creating several eCommerces now available online, as well as my journey in dealing with AWS, Heroku, Namecheap, and Ocean Digital as server providers in most of my projects

#php(laravel) #mysql #postgres #redis #ci-cd #heroku #namecheap #digital-ocean #tailwind #vuejs #nodejs #golang #codepipeline #rds #aws-elastic-beanstalk #docker

#### **Education**

July 2018 Trainer position in full-stack web development certificate

**IEEE** 

October 2018 College of languages - English department

**Cihan University - Duhok** 

August 2016 Backend Developer Certificate

Udacity

#### **Technical Skills**

PHP/Laravel, NodeJS/TypeScript, MySQL/\*SQL, HTML5/CSS3, Git Advanced

GO, MongoDB/NoSQL, Redis, Docker, AWS, DevOps Intermediate

ElasticSearch, Meilisearch

Basic

## Languages

Kurdish, Arabic, English Advanced

Turkish Basic

# **Volunteer experience**

- I love volunteer work and have participated in initiatives and organizations such as "Code for Iraq" for more than three years and up to this moment and until now I got two certificates from IEEE Certificates Program.
- I like to help people to find their way to programming, and I do some courses on my YouTube channel under the name (Rabeea Ali) and also write articles.